<zodiac_signs>
    <sign>
        <name>Aries</name>
        <start_date>March 21</start_date>
        <end_date>April 19</end_date>
        <description>Dynamic and competitive, Aries are born leaders with a passion for action.</description>
    </sign>
    <sign>
        <name>Taurus</name>
        <start_date>April 20</start_date>
        <end_date>May 20</end_date>
        <description>Taurus are known for their stability, loyalty, and love for comfort and beauty.</description>
    </sign>
    <sign>
        <name>Gemini</name>
        <start_date>May 21</start_date>
        <end_date>June 20</end_date>
        <description>Gemini are versatile and curious individuals with a love for communication and learning.</description>
    </sign>
    <sign>
        <name>Cancer</name>
        <start_date>June 21</start_date>
        <end_date>July 22</end_date>
        <description>Cancers are intuitive and nurturing, often deeply connected to emotions and family.</description>
    </sign>
    <sign>
        <name>Leo</name>
        <start_date>July 23</start_date>
        <end_date>August 22</end_date>
        <description>Leos are confident and passionate leaders with a flair for drama and creativity.</description>
    </sign>
    <sign>
        <name>Virgo</name>
        <start_date>August 23</start_date>
        <end_date>September 22</end_date>
        <description>Virgos are practical and detail-oriented perfectionists, often focused on service and improvement.</description>
    </sign>
    <sign>
        <name>Libra</name>
        <start_date>September 23</start_date>
        <end_date>October 22</end_date>
        <description>Libras are diplomatic and harmonious, valuing fairness, partnerships, and aesthetics.</description>
    </sign>
    <sign>
        <name>Scorpio</name>
        <start_date>October 23</start_date>
        <end_date>November 21</end_date>
        <description>Scorpios are intense and passionate, known for their deep emotions, determination, and mystery.</description>
    </sign>
    <sign>
        <name>Sagittarius</name>
        <start_date>November 22</start_date>
        <end_date>December 21</end_date>
        <description>Sagittarians are adventurous and optimistic, with a love for freedom, travel, and philosophical pursuits.</description>
    </sign>
    <sign>
        <name>Capricorn</name>
        <start_date>December 22</start_date>
        <end_date>January 19</end_date>
        <description>Capricorns are ambitious and disciplined, driven by success, stability, and practicality.</description>
    </sign>
    <sign>
        <name>Aquarius</name>
        <start_date>January 20</start_date>
        <end_date>February 18</end_date>
        <description>Aquarians are innovative and independent thinkers, often focused on humanitarian causes and intellectual pursuits.</description>
    </sign>
    <sign>
        <name>Pisces</name>
        <start_date>February 19</start_date>
        <end_date>March 20</end_date>
        <description>Pisces are compassionate and imaginative, deeply connected to emotions, spirituality, and creativity.</description>
    </sign>
</zodiac_signs>
